♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
You are watching Amazon Prime,
the network that brought you
your sunscreen in two days.
Amazon Prime-- like
the eighth best way to watch TV.
Hi, Chris, how
was school?
Wait, what's that note
pinned to your backpack?
Bet it's from a girl
in the lunchroom
who wants a taste
of corn dog.
Was that a sex joke?
It's...
I don't know,
shut up.
Oh, dear, it's from
Principal Shepherd.
Peter, he wants to see us
first thing tomorrow.
Oh, Chris is
in trouble.
Sounds like he needs a
little fatherly wisdom.
Better get my pipe.
Peter, I think that's
the wrong kind of pipe.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I haven't been doing
too great in school lately.
Well, that's
very disappointing.
I guess your father and I will
have to talk to the principal
and figure out
how to handle this.
Ah, I wouldn't
worry, Lois.
I never did very well
in school either.
I even failed
homeroom.
Peter Griffin?
There.
Thank you for coming,
Mr. and Mrs. Griffin.
Chris seems to be
struggling in his classes,
and often when kids
have trouble in school,
it's because something
is going on at home.
I haven't been attracted to Lois
for a year and a half.
Principal Shepherd, exactly
how poorly is Chris doing?
Well, right now,
he has a D-minus average.
His only hope is
his history final tomorrow.
If he fails that,
I'm afraid he'll have
to repeat ninth grade.
This... seems more
like a phone call.
Oh, my God.
I-I always knew Chris wasn't
a great student,
but I had no idea
the situation was so dire.
Don't worry, I'll make
sure Chris passes history.
You can count on me.
The same way NASA counted on me
during the Apollo 13 crisis.
All right, I'm gonna
need three coffins--
mahogany with
brass handles--
three new daddies for the
dead astronauts' kids,
and a black
suit for me.
Sir, I think I know a way
we can get them back.
Is it hard?
It might be.
Yeah, we-we've kind
of already decided
we're going in
this direction.
All right, Chris,
you got a lot riding
on this history
exam tomorrow.
I know.
Sam Cooke didn't
know much about history,
and he got shot in a hotel
wearing nothing
but a sports coat and a shoe.
Yeah, that's hilarious, Chris,
but we've got to buckle down.
Now, I'm gonna help you study
by nailing your door shut.
That way, you'll have no
choice but to hit the books.
Oh, crap, I left
my phone in there.
Damn
it, it's nailed shut.
Dad, it looks like
some girl sent you
a picture of her privates.
Oh, crap! Lois!
I don't have the phone!
Stop sending pictures!
I already sent four more!
Chris, put down the phone!
Don't look at those!
Wait a minute,
that's both her hands!
Who the hell is
taking the pictures?!
All right, give me that
phone and get back to work.
And before you
judge your mother--
you did most
of that damage.
Oh.
Hey, Chris.
Just wanted to see
how the studying's going.
You guys, I've been
at this all night,
and I haven't
learned a thing.
There's no way I'm gonna pass
Mr. Harpington's history test.
Oh, come on, Chris.
I'm sure that's
just the nerves talking.
Here, I'll quiz you.
Who said, "We have nothing
to fear but fear itself"?
Scooby-Doo?
No.
Shaggy?
It's nobody on Scooby-Doo.
Wow, Chris,
you, uh...
you really don't
know history.
And if I fail ninth grade,
I won't amount to anything.
I'll end up being
one of those bus drivers
that parents don't
completely trust.
You have a beautiful
child, Mrs. Roberts.
God, poor Chris.
He's studying as hard as he can,
but it doesn't seem to matter.
Well, we got to
do something.
If he doesn't pass this
test, he's gonna have to...
Hey.
...he's gonna have to
repeat ninth grade.
Well, there's not much
we can do about it.
Some people just aren't able
to learn from books.
Well, maybe he
doesn't have to.
What do you mean?
Maybe there's a way
to actually show
Chris history...
with my time machine.
You know, that's really
nice of you, Stewie.
Well, he's my brother.
We've got to
stick together.
Like that two-headed
girl on TLC.
Okay, who wants to taste it,
and who wants to smell it?
All right, we'll just
tell Chris he's dreaming,
because I don't want him
to know about my time machine.
Why not?
Eh, it's like having
a pickup truck.
Once people know you got one,
there go your weekends.
Chris?
Can you hear me?
Huh?
You're dreaming.
I'm dreaming?
Yay! No consequences!
So lifelike!
All right, let's go back
six minutes and try this again.
Chris, you're dreaming
with consequences.
What?
That's right.
We're gonna take you on
a special dream trip
to help you pass
your history test.
You are?
Yes, and there's
so much to learn.
For example, did you know
that Jesus didn't really
die on the cross?
So, what was the
cause of death?
Cocaine and severe trauma
to the colon.
Yeah, I'm gonna need
to see those forms.
Don't look at me like that.
Babe, I told you,
it's a business trip.
All right,
I've got the return pad,
and the time machine is
powering up right now.
We should be leaving any moment.
This thing is awesome.
Stewie, can you believe
Brian built this?
Wait, what?
Oh, hey, come on, guys.
"Who built what"
is not a question
on the history
final, right?
Good point, Brian.
That's why victory
is always Brian's.
You dick!
How much of my stuff
have you taken credit for?!
Hey, everybody?
Just so you know,
I'm straight.
All right, Chris, I
reviewed your textbook,
and I've programmed a tour of
the various historical events
that you'll need to
know for your exam.
So, pay close
attention.
First stop--
Washington, D.C.
The year is 1803.
Ah, the future.
Now, the man at the podium
is Thomas Jefferson.
And this is a very
important moment.
He's trying
to convince Congress
to approve
the Louisiana Purchase.
Come on, guys!
We're getting Oklahoma,
Arkansas, Nebraska, Kansas,
Wyoming, North Dakota,
South Dakota and Louisiana.
What are the chances
all those states suck?
This is Paris, 1920.
This bar is where famous
American writers,
like Ernest Hemingway,
would go for a drink.
Oh, my God,
there he is!
Excuse me, Mr. Hemingway,
can I have a beer with you?
Sure!
I love life
and all the people in it!
Thanks.
And, hey, as a
fellow writer,
I would love to talk
to you about the craft.
I mean, God, if only we could
get rid of these damn arms
and attach the pen directly
to the heart, right?
You guys,
I got his pen!
Now, Chris,
this is Brazil
before the invention
of the soccer ball.
Australia before
the shark-tooth necklace.
And Italy
before pasta.
Ay!
Oh!
Vowel sound!
They were always
a ridiculous people.
Hey, Family Guy, you're lucky
I got a manicotti in the oven,
or I'd bash your face
into a bolognese.
That's two kinds of food.
That's how angry I am.
Oh, my God!
Where are we?!
Omaha Beach, 1944.
This is D-Day.
What's that over there?
Oh, that's
Double D-Day.
♪ She's my cherry pie ♪
♪ Cool drink of water,
such a sweet surprise ♪
♪ Tastes so good... ♪
Nein, nein! No
fire! Ist gut!
Heil hooters!
Be careful.
It could be
a booby trap!
Oh, Otto.
Here we are.
Christmas night, 1776.
The father of our nation,
George Washington,
is about to boldly
cross the Delaware.
What's on his arms?
Those are water wings.
He was terrified
of the water.
Easy!
All right, Chris,
it's 1798,
and we're in the home
of Jane Austen.
Jane Austen?
I don't think she's
on my history test, Stewie.
Oh, I know--
we're just here
to release pent-up
time-travel farts.
Awesome!
Yeah!
Aw, yeah!
Give me some of that!
Mmm, the insides
of men!
This is what
fuels me!
Mmm!
Okay, time for some
recent history.
This is the 1990s.
♪ And I'll tell myself
I'm over you... ♪
This is
the entire 1990s?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Pre-Soviet Russia?
This wasn't
on the manifest.
Yeah, this is kind
of a personal thing.
Hey, Pavlov, you
dog-teasing-dick!
How's this for positive
reinforcement?!
All right,
where to next?
I want to kill
more scientists!
All right, Chris,
that was the British
Parliament, 1912.
Next, we...
I say, that looks like a
young Charlie Chaplin.
Sir, please, take this money and
use it to pursue your dreams.
Danke.
Stewie, I think
that was a young Hitler.
You just gave money
to Hitler!
Yeah, but before all
the crazy stuff.
All right, Chris, let's discuss
what you've learned so far.
Now, what is your biggest
takeaway from our travels?
That you can't take a good nap
with keys in your pocket.
For God's sake, Chris!
You clearly have not
paid attention
to anything we've shown you!
You're absolutely hopeless!
Did you ever consider--
the reason you're having trouble
passing ninth grade is
that you're incapable
of anything else?!
That this is the absolute zenith
of your ability?!
Zenith means top.
No, it means TV.
Ha! Now I'm catching fire.
Damn it, Chris, your problem
isn't book learning,
it's that you're a moron!
This whole trip has been
a complete waste of time!
Screw you, Stewie.
You're a jerk!
And I'm gonna win that bowling
tournament, with or without you!
What is he... what?
He-he doesn't even know what
we're preparing him for!
Chris?
Chris, come back!
Well, we've looked
all over London.
He's nowhere.
I don't know what the
hell we're going to do.
Hey, Stewie!
If I'm such a moron, then how
did I get on a fancy boat?!
See you later, douche bags!
Oh, crap!
Chris is
on the Titanic?!
No, no, it's
okay, Brian.
We'll just go back in time
to before Chris ran off.
Oh, and I took
your fancy smoke detector!
My God, he's got
the return pad!
Brian, we've got to
get on that ship!
Attention, passengers.
The karaoke contest
will begin in five minutes.
Okay, now we've really
got to get on that ship.
Brian, we have
to get on that ship!
It's our only hope
to save Chris.
There! Jump onto
that mooring rope.
We can use it
to pull ourselves up.
Oh, thank God, I wasn't
sure we were gonna make it.
I wasn't worried.
I've faced bigger
challenges.
Like trying to dress
Jonah Hill for the Oscars.
Okay, okay, perfect.
Tell him to stay
exactly that weight.
Yes?
Damn it!
Oh, my God, Brian.
This ship, it's...
it's unbelievable.
It's even more magnificent
than I imagined.
That, Brian.
That.
That's what I was
telling you about.
That's brocade.
Come on, Stewie, we got
to find Chris and the return pad
before it's too late.
All right,
let's split up.
I'll go search
in first class,
you go down
to steerage
and wade through the
gross Irish and Italians.
That's two.
Ugh, God knows what
I'm gonna find in steerage.
Bunch of drunk, fat,
pie-faced Irish fools.
Excuse me, have any of you seen
a blond teenage boy?
Who's asking?
Yeah, who the hell are you?
And I'm the baby!
Chris?
What the hell?
Stewie,
what are you doing?
Uh, dining at the
captain's table.
Everyone at this table
was the first person
to refrigerate
something.
I refrigerated shoes.
Because everybody
likes a cool toe.
Also, I gave the string
quartet the sheet music
for "Highway to
the Danger Zone".
You have the sheet music for
"Highway to the Danger Zone"?
Uh, yeah.
What do you think I
keep in this backpack?
It's all PowerBars
and sheet music.
Stewie, you're supposed
to be looking for Chris.
I did-- he wasn't
in the Turkish bath,
the veranda caf├й or the
Bloody Handkerchief Ball.
Oh, dear.
Relax, Brian, I think
I see Chris right now.
Really? Where?
I'm gonna go ahead
and bet he's the guy
with the whole chicken
stuck on his head.
Hey, you're not Chris.
Pardon me,
that's my hat!
I know this thing's gonna sink,
but I'm having a good time.
Stewie, look!
Chris, there you are!
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Booger Breath
and the Mushroom Tip.
Wh-Which one
of us is which?
Chris, we have got
to get off this boat.
The Titanic was one of the
biggest disasters in history.
Well, if you're
so worried,
why don't you alert
the crew and save everyone?
Because, Chris,
we can't alter the past.
That's the first rule of...
of, uh... uh, dreaming.
Besides, saving
this ship would mean
talking to, like, 80 people,
and I-I'm just not
in that kind of mood right now.
Look, Chris, just give
us that thing you took
so we can
all get home.
Quick, Chris,
Stewie, get on!
To home!
Or I'll just put in
the coordinates.
Damn!
The return pad!
It's been destroyed!
What?!
The whole thing's been
waterlogged!
I'll need to dry it out
and completely rewire it.
This would make
a great movie.
And the parts I need
to fix the return pad
certainly aren't
on this ship.
We have to somehow
get to dry land.
Dry land?!
Stewie, almost everyone
on the Titanic died!
All right,
calm down, Brian.
No-- there's so much
I haven't done.
I've never even
successfully made love
to a woman in
the shower.
Aah, my back!
Should I put my
foot in the soap dish?
Yeah, try that, and maybe
stand on your tippy-toes.
Aah, how does water
make it dry?!
This isn't gonna work.
Brian, this is
our only hope.
The majority
of people
who got on those lifeboats
were women of noble birth.
Now, I've given
us all backstories.
I am Lady Antonia
Tyler Carrington,
the Duchess of Lancashire, the
heir to the Earl of Portsmouth,
and the cousin
of the Countess of Wessex.
Okay, great. And who are we?
I don't know,
you're just two sluts with me.
Hey, there's a lifeboat.
Uh, yeah,
but it's got one
of those funny Southwest
lifeboat attendants.
Hey,
here's a reminder--
as you exit the boat,
don't forget to give us
your extra snacks
because as you know,
we work for peanuts!
That's refreshing.
Most of those guys
are all serious.
There, that one!
It's our last chance.
Hey, they learned it!
What a bunch of pros.
Hello there, sir.
We are three noblewomen
in distress...
Sorry, boat's full.
Um, what if one of us were
to turn this big ship
into a "tug" boat?
Wink, wink.
Wouldn't help you.
You're the fourth person
to offer that,
and I'm kind of spent.
I don't believe this.
Dear God,
we're stuck here.
We're going to drown
on the Titanic.
Oh, no, we're not.
Hey! I said
you can't come on here.
Get out of my way,
you son of a bitch!
Oh, no!
I can't swim without
my striped one-piece!
Everyone move over.
We're getting on this boat.
Please take my baby!
Yeah, I'm sorry,
if I take your baby,
I'm gonna have
to take everyone's baby.
Can you believe
that woman?
Putting me on the spot
in front of everyone.
To home!
You see what
you started?
Wow, Chris.
You just saved
our lives.
Thank you.
Oh, it was
nothing, Brian.
Listen, Chris,
I, um...
I think I owe
you an apology.
I'm not someone
who often makes mistakes,
but, well, I was wrong earlier
when I called you a moron.
No, you were right.
You're the smart one in the
family, and I'm the dumb one.
Oh, you're being too
hard on yourself.
Look, you may not be
"book smart" or "history smart,"
but you're "throw people
off the boat" smart.
And, frankly,
I'm starting to think
that's the best kind to be.
Thanks, Stewie.
Well, looks like
one ship was saved today--
a relation-ship.
Oh, thank God,
we're back.
Wow, what an
adventure!
Thanks, Dream Brian.
Thanks, Dream Stewie.
Brian, Stewie!
I just had the most
amazing dream.
I was on a famous boat
called the Gigantic.
Yeah, he's gonna fail
that test tomorrow.
Well, we gave it our
best shot, Stewie.
It was still a nice thing
you did for your brother.
I suppose.
I just hope that Chris
killing one extra man
on the Titanic didn't alter
anything in the present.
There he is.
"Nigel Harpington."
Wait, "Harpington"?
Isn't that the name of
Chris' history teacher?
Yes, I think
you're right.
That must be
his ancestor.
Which means that Chris'
history teacher was never born.
Hey, everybody,
I'm Teacher Doug,
and I don't believe
in tests.
Yay!
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru